AKKEWACH YODSOMBOON

Software Developer

akkewach.yodsomboon@gmail.com 084-004-5946 https://akkewach.site https://github.com/akkewacheiei



Profile

Date of Birth: May 7,1998

Gender: Male **Nationality:** Thai

Language: Thai (Native), English (Basic)

My Introduction

I am a software developer with 4 years of experience in developing both websites and applications, I continue to further my skills to grow in this field.

Work Experience

JUL 2024 - PRESENT Workmotion Co.,Ltd.

Full Stack Developer

- Full-stack development with Next.js/Nuxt.js and Node.js/NestJS, including REST API design.
- ITD Expert Anywhere Online platform enabling SMEs to book and consult with business experts.
- Rebalance Clinic management platform covering patient records, sales orders, stock management, and refund processes.
- INDY T-Shirt T-shirt ordering and production system with dynamic work order generation and inventory management.

AUG 2020 - JAN 2024 Wellliness Co.,Ltd.

Full Stack Developer

- Working collaboratively with a team of UX/UI designers and fitness coaches.
- Developed a platform for online fitness courses that generates workout video schedules tailored to each individual user.
- Continuously adapt and improve the software's features.

Education

2016 - 2020 Rajamangala University of Technology Thanyaburi

Bachelor Degrees

Computer Engineering Department, Faculty of Engineering

Skills

Frontend

- Next.js, Nuxt.js
- React.js, Vue.js
- React Native
- Redux
- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- Ant Design
- TailwindCSS
- Bootstrap

Backend

- Node.js
- Express.js
- Nest.js (Basic)
- REST API
- MongoDB
- MySQL
- ORM (Sequelize)

DevOps / Deployment

- PM2 process manager
- Nginx reverse proxy
- CI/CD pipelines
- Docker (Basic)
- Deployment on Linux server (Ubuntu, DigitalOcean)